ML Ideas:

- FPP or EPP?
- Identify Art Movements
- (Diversifai) Is Your data set demographically balanced


disney research notes (quotes, links, etc)

fastpass+:
FastPass+’s reliance on websites and smart phone apps is largely lauded, and the most passionate advocates will gladly tell you how much they appreciate the fact that they can even make their reservations 60 days in advance, or link their ride times with the rest of their family’s. And the fact that a whole slew of additional attractions, such as older or minor rides and nighttime shows, have been added to the FastPass-eligible list is applauded.
https://orlandoinformer.com/2014/rumor-round-up-march-22-fastpass-plus-controversy/

Pluses and minuses. I like being able to select ahead but 3 picks/1 park is inadequate for a day. And signed they’ve rolled out widely, ice noticed wait times increase significantly. The old system balanced traffic better. So there is room for improvement!
Wayne Walker
https://orlandoinformer.com/2014/rumor-round-up-march-22-fastpass-plus-controversy/

The article didn’t mention what I think is the most glaring problem with FP+, though several commenters did — 3 attractions is just not nearly enough for one day, when you could get five or six under the Legacy system.  I love the new technology features of FP+ but they have got to bump it up to four or five attractions or they will not see me coming as often.
fosterfest
https://orlandoinformer.com/2014/rumor-round-up-march-22-fastpass-plus-controversy/

“No longer does the ‘amazing race’ happen when the rope drop occurs where people run to FastPass locations that were decentralized,” noted Jim McPhee, Senior Vice President, Walt Disney World Parks

FastPass+ is being used by 40% more people than the previous system was, according to Disney Parks and Resorts chairman Tom Staggs, who also added that Disney’s guests are experiencing more attractions and exploring the parks more extensively than they did while using the original FastPass, spending less time “running around grabbing passes.”.
https://insidethemagic.net/2014/05/development-of-fastpass-delivers-freedom-as-walt-disney-world-personalizes-vacations-with-more-mymagic-planned/

https://insidethemagic.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/IMG_9897-550x412.jpg
https://insidethemagic.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/FP21-550x412.jpg

That’s right, guests no longer have to deal with the old “pick 3” process when scheduling their FastPass+ lineup! You basically start by picking members of your FastPass+ party, and then select your park. You then select a timeframe and date (Morning, Afternoon, Evening, specific time, etc). Then, you just select your adventure from a list of attractions and time slots. Boom! Easier than ever!
https://insidethemagic.net/2016/04/new-fastpass-plus-options-greatly-improve-my-disney-experience-app-walt-world/
This is awesome….
Often in the past, I would have to book three fast-passes when I only had intentions of using one.
Thanks for the change….it’ll open up passes for others. Well done Disney
Charles
https://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog/2016/04/new-fastpass-enhancements-at-walt-disney-world-resort/

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xPvatp8W5Lk

mdx:
Disney has just released a new version of the app with a new design, a new homepage which shows your entire days plans, and better navigation.

The new version 2.0 of ‘My Disney Experience’ has a new look and feel, with a new homepage showing your day’s plans, improved navigation, and is overall much quicker to use. … The previous version was widely panned by Disney fans as being slow and not well designed.   We tested the new app today and it seems like a big improvement.  It was very, very fast.
https://www.disneydining.com/disney-experience-app-version-2/
I love the app, when it first rolled out I wanted to throw the thing at the wall. But with the updates, it is fast and easy to use.
KatMaria
https://forums.wdwmagic.com/threads/my-disney-experience-app.882000/
The update, all around...performance, features, fluidity, mapping, 3D visuals, searching, everything,...is almost startling. I know that seems gushing, but update and try, you'll see.
Dan Murphy
https://www.disboards.com/threads/my-disney-experience-android-app-update-great.3294492/
